<DOC DOCNO="bc/p2.5_a2e/00/p2.5_a2e_0035@0035@p2.5_a2e@bc@en@on">
<ENAMEX TYPE="DATE">The twenty - fifth of January</ENAMEX> is the initial date for holding the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Arab</ENAMEX> and international conference for the support of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Lebanon</ENAMEX> , or <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Paris Three</ENAMEX> ; and the preparations , according to the Minister of Finance , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Jihad Azour</ENAMEX> , are still underway in spite of what is going on in the street .
The government of Prime Minister <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Fouad Al Siniora</ENAMEX> has worked since it was established to get <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Lebanon</ENAMEX> out of the financial crisis and to improve the economic situation , and it has worked also for holding this conference .
Minister <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Azour</ENAMEX> said --
What if quote unquote the government of Prime Minister <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Fouad Al Siniora</ENAMEX> fell , what would be the destiny of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">Paris Three</ENAMEX> ?
I , let me , what is -- we , the way we are working , these are questions I have no answer for , but the answer I do have is to continue preparation and persistence .
</DOC>
