<DOC DOCNO="bc/p2.5_a2e/00/p2.5_a2e_0024@0024@p2.5_a2e@bc@en@on">
First ah as we know that <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Al - Sadr</ENAMEX> current had announced the suspension of its participation in the government and the parliament in opposition to the meeting of <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Bush</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Al Maliki</ENAMEX> , the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Iraqi</ENAMEX> Prime Minister .
This is not the first time an <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Iraqi</ENAMEX> Prime Minister has met with President <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Bush</ENAMEX> , right ?
In the Name of Allah , the Most Beneficent , the Most Merciful .
Naturally , the situation that Iraq is going through lately , is a situation , I mean , ah it is going through a crisis and dangerous escalation in %pw acts of violence and terrorism .
believes that all these acts of violence or what is going on in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX> and the deterioration of the situation , that the reason for that is the occupation forces .
So , when the <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Al - Sadr</ENAMEX> current opposed ah ah the visit or the meeting of Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Al - Maliki</ENAMEX> with <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Bush</ENAMEX> , considering the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Americans</ENAMEX> are responsible , a direct responsibility , for what is happening in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX> .
Certainly , certainly , but now things started to get more dangerous and to get more heated , and the security situations in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX> started to deteriorate bit by bit , so actually we have reached a stage the street would not be able to handle what is going on .
Definitely , it is ah a political justification , or a political position that the <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Al - Sadr</ENAMEX> current adopted , I hope , I mean , that there would be a round of dialogue between ah the political powers and the government in order to coordinate the position before announcing it .
Are you going to apply the same thing you did with the Prime Minister to <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Bush</ENAMEX> 's meeting with <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Abd - al Aziz al - Hakim</ENAMEX> ?
No , naturally , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the Supreme Council</ENAMEX> has its own policy , and I believe it is a party that has its political plan .
No , certainly <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Abd al - Aziz al - Hakim</ENAMEX> is a political man , who has his political project , but we are demanding the Prime %pw the Prime Minister , he has the bigger authority in the administration of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE">Iraq</ENAMEX> as a whole , but Abd al - Aziz al - Hakim or Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Abd al - Aziz al - Hakim</ENAMEX> is a contributing party in the political process , and he has his political role .
Ok .
<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Abd al - Aziz al - Hakim</ENAMEX> , I mean , you want to say , has his political program ; his political program is different from your program ?
Definitely , we disagree with the brothers in <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the Supreme Council</ENAMEX> with our political project , we have a project of resistance , reform and change .
They have a project of the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Americans</ENAMEX> .
No , no , not change and reform , but they do not believe in resistance at the time being , and so they entered the political process from its beginning , before the fall of the regime .
%pw Yes .
</DOC>
