<DOC DOCNO="bc/p2.5_a2e/00/p2.5_a2e_0044@0044@p2.5_a2e@bc@en@on">
I mean , uh , I mean , %pw could an attractive offer come along , uh , %pw that would urge Speaker <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Nabih Berri</ENAMEX> to , uh , %pw call once again upon the discussion table ?
Uh , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Abir</ENAMEX> , %pw , I mean , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG">the 14 February Forces</ENAMEX> mainly tried to manipulate , uh , <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Shiite</ENAMEX> bilateralism , thinking there could be certain differences , well , or political diversity , or , or paradoxes , or possibly political differences between Speaker <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Berri</ENAMEX> on the one hand and the resistance and Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Nasrallah</ENAMEX> on the other .
Speaker <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Berri</ENAMEX> , today , and until the last moments of the divorce kept saying that the marriage could still be patched up , the combination of national accord and dialog were still possible , but when all these windows were closed , the final cure was cauterization , as you mentioned at the beginning of the episode .
Of course , today there have been attempts to revive Speaker <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Berri</ENAMEX> 's role in this direction , but let 's admit that what 's going on today in <ENAMEX TYPE="LOC">Martyr Square</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="LOC">Riyadh Al - Sulh Square</ENAMEX> dictates a new national political game to Speaker <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Berri</ENAMEX> , as well as all the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP">Lebanese</ENAMEX> parties involved .
Today there can be no return to any discussion table or dialog table to discuss matters that have become part of the past .
</DOC>
